Ziemia.
Ogień.
Powietrze.
Woda.
Only the Avatar
can master all four elements
and bring balance to the world.
Amon's revolution
grows stronger by the day.
First, he attacked
the bending arena.
Then it was discovered
that hiroshi sato
was the mastermind
behind the equalist gloves
and mecha-tanks.
And most recently, amon ambushed
councilman Tarrlok,
took his bending,
and nearly captured
the Avatar as well.
Everyone is on edge wondering,
where will amon strike next?
[Somber music]
♪
Daddy, you're home.
We waited up for you.
Is Korra okay?
Yes, she's fine, sweetie.
I was scared.
I thought she wasn't
coming back.
I'm sorry you were scared,
but everything is going
to be fine now.
I promise.
Mmm.
The food tastes amazing, pema.
I'm finally starting
to feel like myself again.
We're so thankful
you're home safe.
Let me help.
Korra, I realize
you've been through a lot,
but I need to know
everything that happened.
Well, first off,
Tarrlok isn't who he says he is.
He's yakone's son.
It all makes sense now.
That's how Tarrlok was able
to bloodbend us
without a full moon.
But how did you escape?
And where's Tarrlok?
Amon captured him
and took his bending.
- What?
- Yeah.
He showed up out of nowhere.
He almost got me too.
This is very disturbing news.
Amon is becoming emboldened.
Taking out a councilman,
almost capturing the Avatar...
I fear amon is entering
his end game.
[Crying out]
Pema, are you all right?
The baby is just kicking
really hard, is all.
I'm fine.
Should I get Tenzin?
No reason to worry him.
It's nothing.
Can I get some hot water?
Korra needs more tea.
You're a firebender.
Boil it yourself.
I'm gonna step out
in case you two want to talk.
Is there something
we need to talk about?
I've noticed
how you treat Korra.
How you acted
when she was missing.
You have feelings
for her, don't you?
What?
No.
She was taken
by a crazy bloodbender.
How did you expect me to act?
I like Korra.
But you've been keeping
the truth from me
this whole time.
The truth?
About what?
You're really
gonna make me say it?
Yes, because I don't know
what you're talking about.
The kiss, Mako.
I know.
Iwell...
Bolin told you, didn't he?
Don't blame your brother
for what you did.
Do you have feelings
for Korra or not?
Look, things are crazy
right now.
Can we deal with
our relationship problems later?
Well, there might not
be any relationship
to worry about later.
Asami.
[Sighs]
Lin, um, I-I need
to ask you a favor.
It would mean the world to me,
but I-I know it could be
a potentially awkward situation.
Furthermore...
Spit it out already.
Will you stay here and watch
over pema and the children
while I meet with the council?
With everything
that's happened lately,
I want to be sure
my family is in safe hands.
Of course I'll help,
old friend.
I didn't realize
you two were out here.
Pema!
Uh, yes, yes.
Lin has agreed
to help out around here
and keep an eye on things
while I'm away.
Thank you.
I could use
the extra pair of hands.
[Giggling]
Would you mind
giving him a bath?
He's filthy.
[Laughing]
This is not
what I signed on for.
Thank you, lin.
Oogi, yip, yip.
[Oogi growling]
I got to poo.
Really bad.
Ooh! Ah!
Ugh!
Do you know
where my keys are?
I can't find them anywhere.
No, dear.
- Oh, found them.
- Good, dear.
Don't wait up for me.
This council session will
probably go late into the night.
[Knocking]
The door, dear.
We're here to fix
a spider-rat problem.
I didn't call
an exterminator.
Dear?
[Growling]
[Grunts]
Ugh!
- Aah!
- Oof!
Aah!
Oh, I'm so relieved to see you.
The other council members,
are they all right?
I'm afraid not.
I just received a call
from chief saikhan.
They've all been captured.
This can't be happening.
The leadership
of Republic city
is in your hands now.
[Explosion]
[Dramatic music]
It is a tragic day indeed!
All right, kids.
Time to go inside.
We heard explosions.
What's going on?
Republic city
is under attack.
I've dreamed of this day
for so long.
Yes.
The time has come
for the equalists
to claim Republic city
as their own.
[Sirens blaring]
Where did you say
you parked the car?
It's right
around here somewhere.
There it is.
Wow, nice parking job.
Hey, you guys got arrested
and left me alone with the car.
I made it very clear
I don't know how to drive.
All things considered,
you did a great job.
But how are we gonna pay
for all these parking tickets?
[Gasps]
Relax, the city's
under attack.
The police have more important
things to worry about.
This'll come in handy.
Why don't you sit in back
with Korra?
I think I will.
- Everything all right?
- Yeah.
Everything's terrific.
[Tires screeching]
Car!
Oh, we're good.
[Sirens blaring]
Chief, air unit seven
was just taken out
by an equalist airship.
They've crashed
into the harbor.
Send a river rescue unit.
Chief, all river rescue ships
have been sabotaged.
What?
Chief saikhan.
Tenzin, am I glad to see you.
I was afraid
you'd been captured too.
I'm the only
council member left.
What's the status?
Amon has launched
simultaneous attacks
across the boroughs.
The police are trying
to regain control,
but we're spread too thin.
- I need to send a wire.
- To whom, councilman?
The General
of the united forces.
[Coughing]
Councilman, your wire
has been sent.
Chief, the phone lines
just went dead.
[Alarm sounding]
[Alarm dying out]
[Gasps]
Catch.
Saikhan, the vents!
[Coughing]
We need
to evacuate immediately.
Everyone stay close to me.
[All gasp]
Not these
mecha-tanks again.
- Aah!
- Oof!
- Ugh!
[Grunting]
Aah!
[Straining]
[Grunting]
[Groans]
Saikhan, no.
[All groaning]
[Groans]
Jump!
Ugh!
Aah!
[Grunts]
Ugh!
Aah!
Oh!
[Fighting cry]
[Groans] Thank you.
Tenzin has escaped
once again.
I can't stand
to see asami fighting
alongside those benders.
We will capture them
before long,
and you will have
your daughter back.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Thank you, kids.
Another moment later,
and I would've been
on my way to amon.
Uh, guys, look.
Oh, no.
Everyone, hide inside
and remain calm.
Aah!
Pull it together, pema.
Didn't I just say,
"remain calm"?
Mommy, what's wrong?
The baby's coming!
Oh, no.
Not now, baby!
[Moaning]
♪
[Grunting]
The children, where are they?
Don't worry.
They're in the other room,
totally safe.
Aah!
[Groans]
Stay away from my dad's
ex-girlfriend.
Ugh! Oof!
Jinora!
You shouldn't be out here!
[Grunting]
Get off our island!
Girls, you need to go
back inside this instant.
Taste my fury!
[Farts]
Meelo, be careful!
[Fighting grunts]
[Farts]
[Roaring]
Never mind.
Take these equalists
and lock them
in the temple's basement.
Nice work, kids.
[Growling]
Dad!
Oh, thank goodness
you're all right.
We caught the bad guys.
You let them fight?
Do you realize
what could've happened?
I would've been toast
if it weren't for your kids.
You should be proud.
You taught them well.
Go on.
Be with your wife.
[Baby wailing]
Pema!
[Baby cries]
Tenzin.
I'm here, pema.
Our new son.
[Cooing]
Hello.
Come, meet your new brother.
A brother?
Well, it's about time.
Welcome.
I'm ikki, and this is jinora
and meelo.
We have a super great family,
and we're so happy
that you're a part of it.
What are you gonna name him?
Can I pick?
We already chose a name.
Rohan.
I'm so sorry
to interrupt, but...
More airships are coming.
Everything's not
gonna be fine,
r:
Is it, daddy?
[Whimpering]
What do you want
to do, Tenzin?
[Sighs]
I need to protect my family
and get them as far away
from this conflict as possible.
If amon got his hands
on my children...
I hate to even think of it.
If you're leaving,
then I'm going with you.
- But...
- No arguments.
You and your family
are the last airbenders.
There's no way in the world
I'm letting amon
take your bending away.
Thank you, lin.
Korra, I want you
to leave this island
and hide for the time being.
- I'm not giving up.
- I'm not asking you to.
I've sent word
to the united forces.
They will be here soon.
And once my family is safe,
I will return.
With the reinforcements, we can
turn the tide in this war.
What you're saying is
we need to be patient.
You're learning well.
Stay safe, Korra.
You too.
Tenzin, if we're leaving,
we'd better do it now.
Oogi, yip, yip.
[Oogi growling]
[Growls]
[Dramatic music]
♪
Go.
We'll hold them off.
Everyone, climb on.
Let's go, girl.
Moustache guy!
[Growling]
Aah!
Nice one, naga.
[Growls]
They're gaining on us!
Faster, oogi!
[Oogi growls]
Whatever happens to me,
don't turn back.
Lin, what are you doing?
[Grunts]
Oof!
Ugh! Aah!
That lady is my hero.
Yes, she is.
[Growling]
[Growls]
Korra, we should get moving.
Ugh!
Tell me where the Avatar is,
and I'll let you
keep your bending.
I won't tell you anything,
you monster.
Very well.
[Somber music]
♪
General, I just received
a wire from the Avatar.
She says amon and his forces
have gained control of the city.
How do you want to respond?
Tell her we will be arriving
in three days time
and that I look forward
to winning back Republic city.
Together.
As you wish, General Iroh.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.Com