Ziemia.
Ogień.
Powietrze.
Woda.
Tylko Avatar może opanować
wszystkie cztery żywioły
i zaprowadzić równowagę na świecie.
Wojna w Republic City.
Po odkryciu, że jej ojciec,
Hiroshi Sato, współpracuje z wrogiem,
Asami zwróciła się przeciwko niemu.
Po kolejnej porażce
w walce z Equalistami,
Lin Beifong zrezygnowała z funkcji
naczelnika sił policyjnych.
Equaliści wciąż wzrastają w siłę.
Kto pomoże Avatarowi powstrzymać Amona
i przywrócić równowagę w mieście?
Księga Pierwsza
Rozdział 8: Spotkanie przeciwieństw
W końcu jesteście.
Witajcie na Wyspie Świątyni Powietrza.
Waszym nowym domu.
Tak, witajcie w moim domu.
Ale z ciebie mały słodki chłopiec.
Co to za dziwne stworzenie?
To ognista fretka,
pospolity nadrzewny ssak zamieszkujący
lasy bambusowe na południe od Królestwa Ziemii.
Prawda, że jest słodki!
Hip hip, leć bizonie, leć!
Dziękuję za wysłanie nam
pomocników do przeprowadzki.
Tak, byli wspaniali.
Niestrudzeni pracownicy.
Widzę, że zabrałaś kilka rzeczy.
Uwierz mi, mogło być gorzej.
Nie ma problemu,
jesteście tutaj mile widziani.
Jesteś ładna. Mogę dotknąć twoich włosów?
Wygląda na to, że mam konkurencję
Pora na oprowadzenie was.
Latające bizony żyją
w tych jaskiniach na dole.
A to jest świątynia, którą wybudował pradziadek Aang.
A w tym szarym domu jest jadalnia.
Mam kilka pytań.
Czy to wszystko na tej wyspie?
Czy to tutaj trenujecie magię powietrza?
Czy będziemy się musieli ubierać jak ci pomocnicy?
Czy każdy z nas dostanie latającego bizona?
I ostatnie pytanie, ile jest drzew na tej wyspie?
Tak, tak, nie, nie, 10 552.
Więc gdzie się zatrzymamy?
Jesteś chłopcem, chłopcy
zamieszkają w części mężczyzn.
Z chęcią pokaże wam sypialnie mężczyzn.
Jestem mężczyzną.
Meelo, dlaczego nie pójdziesz z chłopakami?
Do zobaczenia wkrótce, piękna dziewczyno.
Ikki i ja pokażemy ci twój pokój, tędy.
Asami, wiesz, że Korra lubi Mako?
Oh, uh, nie zdawałam
sobie z tego sprawy.
- Hej!
- Spadaj, Ikki.
Więc... to twój pokój.
Wiem, że wygląda nieco wiejsko w porównaniu
do tego, w którym mieszkałaś na codzień.
Myślę, że jest naprawdę uroczy,
a najważniejsze jest to,
że nie przypomina mi mojego ojca.
Dziękuję za gościnę.
Ikki, przysięgam, że jeśli
nie zostawisz nas w spokoju...
Tenzin! Wejdź, proszę.
Dzień dobry, moje panie.
Asami, witaj na wyspie.
Dziękuję za pomoc.
Beifong została zastąpiona przez Saikhana.
Będzie ogłoszony nowym szefem sił policyjnych.
Myślę, że powinniśmy to zobaczyć.
To był zaszyt pracować dla
naczelnik Beifong tyle lat.
Życzę jej szybkiego powrotu do zdrowia.
Z wielką pokorą przejmuję jej
miejsce jako nowy szef policji.
Republic City stoi w obliczu zagrożenia,
którego świat jeszcze nie widział.
Ale jest człowiek, który potrafił skutecznie
walczyć z Amonem, to radny Tarlokk.
Dlatego w każdej sprawie związanej z Equalistami,
będę zwracał się bezpośrednio do niego.
Siły policyjne dostarczą wszystkiego co potrzebne,
by wesprzeć radnego i jego siły specjalne.
Dopóki sytuacja się nie uspokoi.
Co ten krętacz Tarlokk kombinuje?
Tarlokk, nie wiem w jaki sposób
trzymasz Saikhana w garści,
ale wątpię, czy to jest zgodne z prawem.
Oh Tenzin, zawsze masz jakieś teorie spiskowe.
Może Saikhan poprostu dostrzegł moje działania
i chce tego, co dla miasta najlepsze?
Wow, Avatar Korra, długo się nie widzieliśmy.
Teraz, gdy już twoje zawody Pro-bendingu się zakończyły,
liczę na twój powrót do moich sił specjalnych.
Zapomnij, nie przystąpię ponownie
do twojego próżnego projektu.
Niemiło jest mi to słyszeć, ale mam nadzieję,
że zmienisz zdanie, tak jak już to raz zrobiłaś.
Tenzin nie mylił się w stosunku do ciebie.
Manipulowałeś mną, mainipulowałeś Beifong
a teraz manipulujesz nowym naczelnikiem.
Mam dla ciebie wiadomość. Ty potrzebujesz mnie,
ale ja nie potrzebuję ciebie. Jestem Avatarem.
Nie do końca, jesteś raczej niecałkowiecie wyszkolonym Avatarem.
Jak tam twoje treningi magii powietrza.
Zrobiłaś jakiś znaczący postęp?
Tak myślałem.
Jeśli nie chcesz być częścią moich sił specjalnych,
najlepiej zrobisz nie wchodząc mi w drogę.
Nie rozumiem, co jest z mną nie tak.
Poznałam praktycznie wszystkie ruchy,
ale nie mogę wytworzyć choćby
małego podmuchu powietrza. Jestem porażką.
Wcale nie. Musisz się przełamać.
Wspaniała porada. Od razu mi pomogła.
Nie skończyłem jeszcze.
Widzisz, Aang nie tylko
korzystał z rad swoich nauczycieli.
ale też z doświadczeń
swoich byłych wcieleń.
Miałaś kiedyś kontakt ze swoimi
wcześniejszymi wcieleniami?
Nie, oczywiście, że nie. Nie dowiadziałeś
się tego od Białego Lotosu?
Jestem też duchową porażką.
Mogłaś mieć kontakt bez zdawania sobie z tego sprawy.
Być może uznałaś, że to był sen.
Może. Miałam kilka dziwnych halucynacji,
ale ciężko jest mi sobie je przypomnieć.
Did you see any of the previous
Avatars in these visions?
I saw Aang. It seemed like he was in trouble.
What do you think it means?
I don't know. But I urge you
to meditate on these visions.
I believe Aang's spirit must be
trying to tell you something.
Korra.Are you out here?
Korra!
Here you are.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Come on, what's wrong?
You can tell us.
How am I supposed to save this city, when I can't even learn airbending?
I'm the worse Avatar ever. I just feel...alone.
That's non-sense, you're amazing.
Yeah and remember, Aang hadn't mastered all the elements while
battling the Fire Nation. He was just a little kid.
And he wasn't alone, he had
his friends to help him.
Look the arena might
be shut down,
but we're still a team, the New Team Avatar!
We got your back Korra and we
can save the city, together.
Yeah, let's do it.
Yeah, let's do it!
What are we doing?
Get ready, Republic City.
You are about to be patrolled by Team Avatar.
Asami you always know how to accessorize your outfits.
I figure one way to fight Equalists is to use an Equalist weapon.
All right, let's ride.
Naga away!
Alright, scratch that, any other ideas?
Hmm. I think I have the answer.
You think this will do?
I like the New Team Avatar's style.
Unit 2-16 cancel that 10-58 in army
tower.Come back to the station, over.
My dad had police scanners installed in
all his cars, I guess now I know why.
All available units, level four
alert, jailbreak at headquarters.
Officers down electric unit. Chi-blockers and Equalist
convoy are still at large armed and dangerous
last seen heading east. I repeat
level four alert Equalist jailbreak.
Chi-blockers!
Let's get them!
Korra, Bolin, give me a ramp now!
Hold me up, we got to make this turn.
They don't know we made the turn.
Get ready.
Avatar Korra, what do
you think you're doing?
Oh hey Tarlokk, nice for you to show up finally.
Here, we captured these escaped convicts for you.
What you did was tear up the city and impede the real
authorities in their pursuit of these criminals.
That's funny, I didn't see your little
task force or the cops the whole time.
If it wasn't for Team Avatar,
they would have gotten away.
This is your last warning,
stay out of my way!
Republic city stand as
a beacon of freedom,
but the Equalists are using
that freedom to tear it down.
The law I have proposed would make it illegal
for anyone to be a member of the Equalists
or even be associated with them.
It also puts into effect a curfew insuring all
non-benders are in their own homes by night fall.
This is going too far Tarlokk, you can't punish
all non-benders for the actions of a few.
That kind of cowardness will cause our city to fall
into Amon's hands. We must pass this law.
All in favor.
All available unit please respond to
the 50-600 block at Dragon plattsburo.
Equalists have taken the street, consider them
armed and dangerous. Proceed with caution.
I'll go front.
After you.
What a gentlemen, thanks.
Why is the power out?
Wait a second, these people
aren't armed or dangerous.
It sure doesn't look that way.
All non-benders return to
your homes immediately.
Yeah, as soon as your
turn our power back on.
Disperse or you will all be arrested.
You benders can't treat us this way.
Mommy, look! It's the Avatar.
Please help us. You're our Avatar too.
Everyone please stay calm,
I'm gonna put a stop to this.
Tarlokk you need to turn the power
back on and leave these people alone.
Avatar Korra you and your
playmate have no business here.
We're not going anywhere. You don't have the right
to treat these innocent people like criminals.
This is an Equalist rally, there
isn't anything innocent about it.
They are not Equalist, they are just
normal people who wants their rights back.
They are the enemy. Rounds
up all these Equalists.
Stop!
Hey! Let me go.
You're under arrest.
What! You can't do that.
Yeah, I can. She's a non-bender out past curfew
and her father is a known Equalist conspirator.
Let her go.
Arrest him and his brother.
Tarlokk!
Unless you want to join your friends in prison, I suggest
you put those down and go back to the Air Temple.
Korra, listen to him, it's not worth it.
We'll be alright.
Don't worry I'll call Tenzin.
He can get you out.
So sad to see your little Team Avatar
broken up. You had a good run.
This isn't over Tarlokk.
Oh, I believe it is. Take them away.
Hey.
I came as fast as I could.
Are your friends alright?
I don't know, these knuckleheads
won't tell me anything.
I'll take care of this.
Saikhan, a word please?
Councilman Tenzin, I'm pretty swarmed at the moment.
Can this wait?
No it cannot. Three of Avatar Korra's
friends were wrongly arrested tonight.
I'd like you to release
them immediately.
They're not going anywhere. They were
interfering with police business.
Your so-called police business was rounding up
innocent people and claiming they were Equalists.
They should be released too.
All Equalist suspects are
being detained indefinitely.
They'll be free, if and when the task force
deems they are no longer a threat.
Those people are entitled to
due process under the law.
You'll have to take that with
councilman Tarlokk.
Oh, I plan to. At the council
meeting, first thing in the morning.
You're officially the worse
chief of police ever!
Calm down, Korra. I'll get this sorted
out, we just need to be patient.
But you really are the worst...
ever.
Wake up Naga, let's go.
Wait for me here, girl.
Don't worry, I'll be alright.
You and I need to talk.
Are any of the other
council members here?
I believe everyone has
gone home for the night.
Then you should do the same.
Are you sure, sir?
Leave us.
You obviously have something on your mind.
Spit it out.
Don't you see? You're doing exactly
what Amon says is wrong with benders.
You are using your power to
oppress and intimidate people.
And you don't?
Of...of course not!
Isn't that what you came here to do?
Intimidate me into releasing your friends?
See that's what I admire about you Korra.
Your willingness to go to extremes
in order to get what you want.
It is a quality we both share.
You and I are nothing alike.
Look, I'll make you a deal.
You fall in line and do what I say
and I'll release your friend.
That's why you arrested them? To get to me?
I need your answer.
No. You might be able to manipulate
chief Saikhan into following you,
but it won't work on me.
You will regret that decision.
You need to be stopped.
You're just as bad as Amon.
I've tried to work with you Korra,
but you have made it impossible.
Still think I'm a half-baked Avatar?
What are you gonna do now?
You're all out of water pal.
You're in my way, Avatar.
And you need to be removed.
You're...you're a...
bloodbender?
Very observant.
It's not a full moon.
How...how are you doing this?
There are a lot of things
you don't know about me.
Where are you taking me?
Somewhere where no one will find you.
Say goodbye to Republic City, Avatar Korra.
You'll never see it again.
You can't do this! Let me out!
Transcribed then subtitled then synced
by Patrick of Addic7ed.com